Guide to the Stanford University, Office of Undergraduate Admissions, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Admissions film outakes, circa 1984-1985; Accession ARCH-2002-265
  - Supers -- Original, 1980s; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 3)
  - Exterior Mos, Barns, Studcuts, Guard, Etc., 1980s; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 3)
  - Libraries -- J. Krasner Government Doc, Special Collections -- Mos, 1980s; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 3)
  - Graduation -- Sync (1/2), 1980s; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 3)
  - Graduation -- Mos & Wild sound (2/2), 1980s; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 3)
  - Condi and Ali, 1980s; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 3)
  - Betsy Randolph Dinenr Gootage (2/2), 1980s; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 3)
  - Interior Mos, 1980s; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 3)
  - Stanford Admissions Film Project (Fine Cut), 1980s; 6 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 4)
  - Page Konrad stanford Admissions Rolls 20, 1980s; 1 film reel(s) (35mm) (Box 4)
  - Brad Efron - Bart Bernstein -- not edge coded, 1980s; 6 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 4)
  - 4 Foreign Students (Sync, Mos), 1980s; 6 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 4)
  - The 2 Frat Bros -- Kevin and Chris Interview, 1980s; 6 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 4)
  - Kathy Olmstead, 1980s; 6 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 4)
  - Page Konrad Stanford Admissions Roll No. 1, 3/7/1985; 6 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 5)
  - Page Konrad/Stanford Comm Stanford Admissions' St. Band Roll No. 3, 3/11/1985; 6 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 5)
  - Page Konrad Stanford Admissions Roll No. 4, 3/26/1985; 6 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 5)
  - P. Konrad Stanford Admissions Roll No. 6-0SR 7424, 4/4/1985; 6 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 5)
  - P. Konrad Stanford Admissions Roll No. 7-SR 7522, 4/4/1985; 6 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 5)
  - P. Konrad Stanford Admissions Roll No. CR 8-CP-13877, 5/8/1985; 6 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 5)
  - P. Konrad Stanford Admissions Roll No. 9-SR-7424, 5/8/1985; 6 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 5)
  - P. Konrad Stanford Admissions Roll No. 10-SR-7522, 5/8/1985; 6 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 5)
  - P. Konrad Stanford Admissions Roll No. 18-SR 7522, 4/23/1985; 6 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 5)
  - P. Konrad Stanford Admissions Roll No. 18-A 19, 3/10/1985; 6 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 5)
  - P. Konrad Stanford Admissions Roll No. 17-SR 7424, 4/23/1985; 6 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 5)
  - P. Konrad Stanford Admissions Roll No. 15-SR-7424, 5/16/1985; 6 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 5)
  - P. Konrad Stanford Admissions Roll No. 14-SR-7522, 5/6/1985; 6 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 5)
  - P. Konrad Stanford Admissions Roll No. 13-SR-7424, 5/11/1985; 6 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 5)
  - P. Konrad Stanford Admissions Roll No. 12-SR-7522, 5/11/1985; 6 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 5)
  - P. Konrad Stanford Admissions Roll No. 11-CP-13877, 5/9/1985; 6 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 5)
  - P. Konrad Stanford Admissions Roll No. 21, 5/23/1985; 6 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 6)
  - P. Konrad Stanford Admissions Roll No. 22, 5/23/1985; 6 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 6)
  - P. Konrad Stanford Admissions Roll No. 23 (actually 24), 6/3/1985; 6 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 6)
  - P. Konrad Stanford Admissions Roll No. 25, 6/11/1985; 6 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 6)
  - P. Konrad Stanford Admissions Roll No. 29, 6/16/1985; 6 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 6)
  - P. Konrad Stanford Admissions Roll No. 31, 6/24/1985; 6 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 6)
  - P. Konrad Stanford Admissions Roll No. 32, 6/25/1985; 6 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 6)
  - P. Konrad Stanford Admissions Roll No. 33, 7/1/1985; 6 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 6)
  - P. Konrad/W. Chan Stanford Admissions CR#2, 3/7/1985; 6 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 6)
  - P. Konrad Stanford Admissions CR#23-SR, 1985; 6 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 6)
  - P. Konrad/W. Chan Stanford Admissions CR#27-7424, 6/15/1985; 6 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 6)
  - P. Konrad/W. Chan Stanford Admissions CR#28, 6/16/1985; 6 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 6)
  - Shinkman Bernstein #1, 3/5/1985; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
  - Unidentified, 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
  - Unidentified, 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
  - Film-Fair "America FC 145", 2/24/1974; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
  - Stanford Chamber Orchestra -- Charles Fergueson, 1980s; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
  - Brad Efron Wild Sound Take 1, Ambiance, 1980s; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
  - Reel 1 Spruce Studies, 1980s; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
  - Ali and Condi Faculty Club, 1980s; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
  - Graduation, 6/15/1985; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
  - Class Day C. Rice D. Kennedy Garden, 6/15/1985; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
  - Chicano Reception, P. Konrad, 6/15/1985; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
  - Seniors 2nd Interviews, P. Konrad, 6/11/1985; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
  - P. Konrad, Kathy Olmstead, 5/23/1985; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
  - P. Konrad, Hopkins-Giley Beach Ambiance Painting Class, 5/23/1985; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
  - P. Konrad, Hopkins Marine Station Wave Ambiance, Baxter-Lab, 5/23/1985; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
  - P. Konrad, Stanford Birds Betsy Randolph--Kitchen, 5/21/1985; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
  - P. Konrad, Macefest Foreign Students, 5/21/1985; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
  - P. Konrad, Betsy Randolph--Hoover, Chris and Kelvin, 5/21/1985; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
  - P. Konrad Don and Ted Kennedy Hunger Conf. Kids at Boat House, 4/11/1985; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
  - P. Konrad Betsy Randolph, Paul Erlich, 4/11/1985; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
  - P. Konrad, Opening Hunger Conference, 4/8/1985; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
  - P. Konrad, Daily Admission Directors, 4/4/1985; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
  - Jim Adams Daily, Ambiance, 4/4/1985; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
  - Stanford Band, 3/9/1985; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
  - Middlebrook, Sound Roll 3, 3/7/1985; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
  - VTS Class, 3/6/1985; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
  - P. Konrad, Steven Harrison and Ensemble, 3/23/1985; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
  - P. Konrad, D. Kennedy, Joan Krasner, Music Department, 4/23/1985; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
  - P. Konrad, Gibbons, Kennedy and Freshman, 4/11/1985; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
  - Wild Sound -- Memorial Church, 4/10/1985; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
  - P. Konrad, Helliwell Derick Scott, 4/9/1985; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
  - Stanford Unviersity Gospel Choir, Fall Quater Musical, 11/18/1984; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
- Records, Accession ARCH-2005-212
  - 1982 Candidate Review List (Box 1)
  - 1983 Final School Review Binder: Rhode Island – Wyoming (Box 1)
  - 1991 Stanford University Applicant File Binder By High School (Box 1)
  - 1978 Freshman Applicants A-Z Binder (Box 1)
  - 1986 Transfer 2A and Ethnic Reports Binder (Box 1)
  - Transfers 1977-1980 Binder (Box 2)
  - Transfers 1980-1986 Binder (Box 2)
  - Transfer Stats 70s-80s Binder (Box 2)
  - 1975 Freshman Applicants Kwuon – Z Binder (Box 2)
  - 1977 Applicants A – K Binder (Box 2)
  - 1966 Freshman Applicants A – K Binder (Box 2)
  - 1981 Freshman Applicants A – K Binder (Box 2)
  - 1968 Freshman Applicants Status Report By Division Binder (Box 2)
  - 1964-1965/1965-1966 Freshman L – Z Binder (Box 3)
  - Autumn 1978 Admits – Also Ethnic Groups Binder (Box 3)
  - 1975 Candidate Review A – Z Binder (Box 3)
  - Autumn 1979 Admits – Also Ethnic Groups Binder (Box 3)
  - 1975 Admits – Also Applicants By Ethnic Group Binder (Box 3)
  - 1983 Applicants A – K Binder (Box 3)
  - 1982 Applicants L – Z Binder (Box 3)
  - Autumn 1981/1982 Freshman Applicants L – Z Binder (Box 4)
  - 1976 Admits – Also Applicants By Ethnic Group Binder (Box 4)
  - 1971 Freshman Applicants A – K Binder (Box 4)
  - 1983 Freshman Applicants L – Z Binder (Box 4)
  - 1965-1966 Freshmen A – K Binder (Box 4)
  - 1968 Freshmen A – Z Binder (Box 4)
  - Autumn 1977 Admits – Also Ethnic Groups Binder (Box 5)
  - 1991 Freshman Applicants And Ethnic Groups Binder (Box 5)
  - 1991 OH – VI Binder (Box 5)
  - 1982 Admits Binder (Box 5)
  - 1971 Status Report and lists of Minority Applicants Binder (Box 5)
  - 1967-1968/1970-1971 A – K and 1972-1973/1974-1975/1976-1977 A – G Transfers Binder (Box 6)
  - Autumn 1974 Freshman Applicants A – Z Binder (Box 6)
  - 1974 Admits – Also Applicants By Ethnic Group Binder (Box 6)
  - Autumn 1980 Freshman Applicants L – Z Binder (Box 6)
  - 1991 Freshman Applicants RS – ND Binder (Box 6)
  - 1981-82-83-84 Transfer Applicants Binder (Box 7)
  - Autumn 1982 Freshman Applicants A – K Binder (Box 7)
  - 1968-9/1969-70/1970-71 Transfers 3 Year Record Binder (Box 7)
  - 1996 Freshmen L – Z Binder (Box 7)
  - 1968-9/1969-70/1970-1 Freshmen Admissions Ledger P-38 Vol. II Colorado through New Mexico Binder (Box 7)
  - 1991 Freshmen AL – IA Binder (Box 8)
  - 1991 Transfers and Ethnic Groups Binder (Box 8)
  - Autumn 1983 Freshman Admits and Ethnic Groups—All Applicants Binder (Box 8)
  - 1973 Freshman Applicants A – Kyle, James Madison Binder (Box 8)
  - Fall 1979 Freshman Applicants Kyan, Fee Siang – Z Binder (Box 8)
  - 1967/1968/1969/1970/1971 L – Z and 1972/1973/1974/1975/1976/1977 H – Z Transfers Binder (Box 8)
  - Autumn 1975 Freshman Applicants A – Kwong, Raymond P. Binder (Box 9)
  - Autumn 1981 Freshman Admits and Ethnic Groups—All Applicants Binder (Box 9)
  - Fall 1979 Freshman Applicants A – Kwong, Yu Hung Binder (Box 9)
  - 1977 Freshman Applicants Kwok, Shui Tat – Z Binder (Box 9)
  - 1970-1979 Transfer Students Binder (Box 9)
  - Alumni Boston Folder (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 1987 Pubs Folder (“Pubs” = Publications?) (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - 1986 Folder (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - 1985 Folder (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Local College Nights 1985 Folder (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Envelopes, Stationery Fall 1982 and 1983 Folder (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Application Materials Fall 1980 – Copies of What Sent to Press Folder (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - 1981 Folder (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - 1978 Folder (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - 1977 Folder (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - 1976 Folder (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - 1975 Folder (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - 1980 Folder (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - 1979 Folder (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - 1974 Folder (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - 1967 Folder (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - 1968 Folder (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - 1969 Folder (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - 1970 Folder (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - 1973 Folder (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - 1989 Pubs Folder (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - 1990 Folder (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 1991 Folder (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - 1992 Folder (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - 1993 Folder (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - 1994 Folder (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - 1995 Folder (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - 1996 Folder (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - 1997 Folder (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - 1998 Folder (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - 1999 Folder (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Autumn 1980 Freshman Admits and Ethnic Groups – All Applicants Binder (Box 12)
  - 1962-1963/1963-1964 Freshmen L – Z Binder (Box 12)
  - 1963-1964/1964-1965 Freshmen A – K Binder (Box 12)
  - Female Admissions Binder (Box 12)
  - Miscellaneous Stats and Summaries 1960s-1970s and 1980 (loose papers) (Box 12)